[{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679473333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":23187,"timeElapsed":650884},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679478278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4943,"timeElapsed":655830},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679483068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4786,"timeElapsed":660620},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679487605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4534,"timeElapsed":665157},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679495721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":8113,"timeElapsed":673273},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679498325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2602,"timeElapsed":675877},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679502381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4054,"timeElapsed":679933},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679511708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":9323,"timeElapsed":689259},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679518353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6642,"timeElapsed":695904},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679532869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":12920,"timeElapsed":710421},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679535552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2680,"timeElapsed":713104},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679537974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":715526},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679540553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2576,"timeElapsed":718105},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679543768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":721320},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679547048,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3278,"timeElapsed":724600},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679549924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2874,"timeElapsed":727476},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679553984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4057,"timeElapsed":731536},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679556700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2714,"timeElapsed":734252},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679560584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3880,"timeElapsed":738135},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679572887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":10937,"timeElapsed":750439},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679575545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2657,"timeElapsed":753097},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679578374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2827,"timeElapsed":755926},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679580955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2578,"timeElapsed":758507},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679583532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":761084},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679586694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3159,"timeElapsed":764246},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679590014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3318,"timeElapsed":767566},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679592896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2880,"timeElapsed":770448},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679595632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2731,"timeElapsed":773184},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679607583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":10490,"timeElapsed":785135},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679610194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2610,"timeElapsed":787746},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679612439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2242,"timeElapsed":789991},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679615154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2713,"timeElapsed":792706},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679620967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5810,"timeElapsed":798518},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679625269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4300,"timeElapsed":802821},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679628938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3667,"timeElapsed":806490},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679637289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8349,"timeElapsed":814841},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679640128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2838,"timeElapsed":817680},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679658972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":17000,"timeElapsed":836524},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679662199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3224,"timeElapsed":839751},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679666849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4647,"timeElapsed":844400},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679669659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2808,"timeElapsed":847211},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679672301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":849853},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679675324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3021,"timeElapsed":852876},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679678278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2952,"timeElapsed":855830},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679682342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4061,"timeElapsed":859894},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679685256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2912,"timeElapsed":862808},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679698657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":11834,"timeElapsed":876209},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679701204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2545,"timeElapsed":878756},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679704052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2846,"timeElapsed":881604},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679706756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":884308},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679711410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4651,"timeElapsed":888962},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679716320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4908,"timeElapsed":893872},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679720188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3866,"timeElapsed":897740},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679723675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3485,"timeElapsed":901227},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679726613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2936,"timeElapsed":904165},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679737421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9022,"timeElapsed":914973},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679739968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2544,"timeElapsed":917520},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679742898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2928,"timeElapsed":920450},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679746309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3408,"timeElapsed":923860},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679749978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3667,"timeElapsed":927530},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679753073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3092,"timeElapsed":930625},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679757482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4407,"timeElapsed":935034},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679760608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3124,"timeElapsed":938160},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679763261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":940813},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679768633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3774,"timeElapsed":946185},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679771989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3353,"timeElapsed":949541},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679774526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2534,"timeElapsed":952078},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679777198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2670,"timeElapsed":954750},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679780194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2994,"timeElapsed":957746},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679783573,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3377,"timeElapsed":961125},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679789820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6245,"timeElapsed":967372},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679798500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8678,"timeElapsed":976052},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679806362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7860,"timeElapsed":983914},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679809731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":987282},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679822944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11723,"timeElapsed":1000496},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679826949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4003,"timeElapsed":1004501},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679830794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3843,"timeElapsed":1008346},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679833692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2897,"timeElapsed":1011244},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679838172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4476,"timeElapsed":1015723},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679841603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3429,"timeElapsed":1019155},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679844179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":1021731},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679849798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5616,"timeElapsed":1027349},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679853089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3290,"timeElapsed":1030641},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679857900,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3178,"timeElapsed":1035452},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679861133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":1038685},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679863789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":1041341},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679866683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2892,"timeElapsed":1044235},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679873178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6494,"timeElapsed":1050730},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679877742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4562,"timeElapsed":1055294},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679880562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2818,"timeElapsed":1058114},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679885289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4725,"timeElapsed":1062841},{"subjectID":"v4959qdotl","prolificID":"67532b54cc1a79af56e2517f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35d40d4cd9d1e91d65","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679889028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3736,"timeElapsed":1066580}]